export const WORDS = [
  { word: "clach", answer: "a' chlach" },
  { word: "tunnag", answer: "an tunnag" },
  { word: "uisge", answer: "an t-uisge" },
  { word: "feòrag", answer: "an fheòrag" },
  { word: "bàta", answer: "am bàta" },
];


export const WORDS2 = [
  {
      "article": "an tunnag",
      "back": "tunnag",
      "front": "duck",
      "gender": "fem",
      "genitive": "tunnaige",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "tunnagan"
  },
  {
      "back": "snog",
      "front": "nice",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "back": "seo",
      "front": "This is",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "article": "a' phiseag",
      "back": "piseag",
      "front": "kitten",
      "gender": "fem",
      "genitive": "piseige",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "piseagan"
  },
  {
      "article": "a' mhuc",
      "back": "muc",
      "front": "pig",
      "gender": "fem",
      "genitive": "muice",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "mucan"
  },
  {
      "back": "Mòrag",
      "front": "Morag",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "back": "mòr",
      "front": "big",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "back": "math",
      "front": "good",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "back": "Irn bru",
      "front": "Irn Bru",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "back": "gàidhlig",
      "front": "Gaelic",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "back": "Eilidh",
      "front": "Helen",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "back": "dona",
      "front": "bad",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "article": "an cù",
      "back": "cù",
      "front": "dog",
      "gender": "masc",
      "genitive": "coin",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "coin"
  },
  {
      "article": "a' chearc",
      "back": "cearc",
      "front": "chicken",
      "gender": "fem",
      "genitive": "circe",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "cearcan"
  },
  {
      "article": "an cat",
      "back": "cat",
      "front": "cat",
      "gender": "masc",
      "genitive": "cait",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "cait"
  },
  {
      "article": "an caraid",
      "back": "caraid",
      "front": "friend",
      "gender": "masc",
      "genitive": "caraid",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "càirdean"
  },
  {
      "article": "a' chaileag",
      "back": "caileag",
      "front": "girl",
      "gender": "fem",
      "genitive": "caileige",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "caileagan"
  },
  {
      "article": "a' bhò",
      "back": "bò",
      "front": "cow",
      "gender": "fem",
      "genitive": "bà",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "bà"
  },
  {
      "back": "beag",
      "front": "little",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "article": "am balach",
      "back": "balach",
      "front": "boy",
      "gender": "masc",
      "genitive": "balaich",
      "level": "Intro",
      "plural": "balaich"
  },
  {
      "back": "Anna",
      "front": "Anne",
      "level": "Intro"
  },
  {
      "back": "agus",
      "front": "and",
      "level": "Intro"
  }
]